the end of the day
The reason why it's there
is I will keep you safe
It's okay to go ahead and go ahead
The moon will come to the moon
Wow, you like my star shield?
What's up with this guy's body?
There's no way a human can do this stuff.
Spitting fire again? Master!
Don't walk!
Hey, stop jumping around!
We're getting nowhere!
I was hoping my four powers
would be enough, but I guess not.
I'm afraid I haven't mastered
the finger pistols yet,
but I've got a little standard that
you do the job quite nicely All right,
this is my chance to go to the next car.
I thought we were having a fight here.
He thinks he's smart
Got you now.
Nice try, but I saw that
coming from a mile away!
That hurts!
I get it.
You son of a bitch.
Ouchie finger!
This ain't good.
He's got my number now.
Just grazed me.
Sure moves around a lot, though.
I know your weak point.
It's your back, isn't it?
And that's not counting your brain,
which is an obvious weakness, too.
At this rate, it's only a matter
of time before you're finished.
Don't get ahead of yourself, pal.
I got a move that'll get rid
of my weak point easy. Franky!
Invincible!
Eat that!
Now do you give up, Weasel Face?
That's so stupid!
I don't even have a comeback.
Anyway, this is nothing but bad luck!
Bad luck for you!
I mean, did I mention
I was super this week?
It's not a good time to make me angry!
Let me ask you something,
brother: have you ever heard of a?
A creature they call a centaur? Huh?
You mean those things
that are human from the
waist up and like a horse
from the waist down?
Yeah, what about them?
Convert!
No way!
That's ridiculous!
Ranking!
Sent our move! It's backwards!
Your head's supposed to be in
the front, not your crotch!
You call this backwards?
Just wait till I rearrange
your face, weasel boy.
Damn it, you crook-cook!
My awesome noodle fists are all gone!
What am I?
An onion?
If you're an onion, you're going to
make yourself cry if you keep this up.
Just quit while you're ahead.
I won't cry, and I won't quit.
Who said I was going to lose?
After all, I'm what's a CP7's aist.
I may look like I'm having fun, but
I take this mission very seriously.
The government's been
chasing Robin for years,
and I'm not going to be the one to
blow it now that we finally have her.
So maybe you're the one who
should quit while you're ahead.
Now, ramen can boo!
Noodle-nail knockout!
When cutting an onion,
you need to sever the stem and the
root without harming the flesh.
If you chop through the
fiber with one clean stroke,
the surface will retain its glossy shine.
Stop it! Go away!
Come and be!
Blue shot!
You...
you got me!
Huh?
You didn't cut me? Sure,
peeling onions may not be glamorous,
but you have to put love into
every aspect of your cooking.
Kitchen knives aren't for cutting people.
You don't treat them like swords.
However, they did a fine job
of cutting down that armor.
Kitchen knife, bro!
Punk!
My eyes!
They're keeping me!
Let them.
Now, shut your mouth and give up.
Yeah, you wish.
I don't get it.
Why do you want to save that terrible
woman so much in the first place?
Or maybe Nico Robbins got you all fooled.
You want me to tell you the truth, huh?
Think you can take it?
No.
Truth.
Bullshit. Dark.
Mantle.
If you keep talking like that,
I'm going to rearrange your face.
Hold on a sec.
Anything but the face.
Cut it out.
Everyone knows she's bad news.
It's no secret. She's evil. A monster.
Better off dead.
Shut up.
Damn it!
I think my face caved in!
I need a mirror!
You fiend!
You ruined my beautiful
eyes and fabulous teeth!
You're the devil, aren't you?
Hey, your face went back
You're right!
Look, my inner beauty is shining!
It was but a fleeting illusion.
You're guilty of three sins.
Let me list them.
First off, you dared to call
yourself a chef in front of me.
Second, you were
disrespectful to your food.
And third, you insulted my friend.
For that, you'll pay.
Whoa!
You put on a big show, but
you're all barkin' no bite.
Whether you've got two legs or four, you
still seem pretty useless to me. Saint.
No! No!
Looking pretty pathetic, buddy. Shut up!
Shall I give you a hand?
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't you dare!
Just kidding.
Give me a hand.
You ought to be ashamed of
yourself using a line like that.
Yes.
And what was that about four
legs being useless, huh?
I just needed to catch you.
You can't run now.
I hate you, you jerk!
I just want to be me!
Give me my individuality.
Right on the other side of that door behind
you, my friend is waiting to be rescued.
When I say no, I mean no!
Robin Kidpo, secret move!
Poison pasta cutter!
Touch it and die!
Go, go, go, go, go!
You people are pathetic!
Nico Robin has you eating
right out of her hand!
She's betrayed every person she's ever met
and you're here risking
your life to save her.
You're beyond help.
It's time to die
I don't know.
I didn't think you used such a dumb trick!
I let my guard down!
Right!
Oh yeah, cause I'm the dumb one here!
Instead of making excuses,
why don't you tell me what you
want written on your gravestone,
brother?
Oh, I get it.
You don't think this
fight is over yet, do you?
What?
Since you dodged all my punches
so far, I can't really blame ya.
You have no clue how hard I can hit.
It's gonna be a nasty surprise.
Here's my ultimate hammer!
Some entrance.
What the hell have you been doing?
Wow, well as per usual, I've been kicking
ass and what about you been kicking ass?
It's gotten so noisy all of a sudden!
I take it all of the escorts for this
mission have been annihilated then.
Well, we weren't expecting
much from them to begin with.
So it's you you're the bastards
who kidnapped Robin be careful.
They use some pretty weird moves
And who is this?
Based on what Corgi said, he's
probably that new recruit for Cape.
Name's Nero.
He's gone through training,
knows four of the powers.
Ah, damn it.
You're in for it now, you bastard.
Nobody does that to me
and gets away with it.
I'll show you why they call
me the genius of fighting.
Now prepare to die!
Huh?
Hey, new guy.
Let me guess.
You must be Rob Lucci.
Sorry I didn't introduce myself.
Just give me a moment, and
I'll kill this troublemaker.
Our orders were to bring him in alive.
You've let your emotions get
the better of you, it seems.
Well, that just won't do.
I'll give you three seconds
to run for your life.
Three.
Run for my life?
Run from who? Two.
What?
Stop kidding around, okay?
It's not funny!
And one. No!
Don't do it! Chase!
You're nothing more than an
incompetent piece of trash.
You call yourself cp
9 don't make me laugh.
You have to master all six
powers to be one of us rookie.
Khalifa yes on our official report
state the new guy was too weak.
He was therefore deemed worthless
Understood.
These are the agents of justice.
Can't tell what sides evil, huh?
I suppose there's no need to ask.
What you're doing on this train?
Intruder.
Judging by the way you open the door,
I know exactly the kind of impatient
people we're dealing with. Yeah.
Guess you'll have to excuse my manners.
You've come to rescue Nico Robin?
That is a mistake.
Listen, her problem is one
that's beyond your comprehension.
You see, there are some people in this
world who were just born under a bad sign.
People who are, for the sake of
everyone else, better off dead.
For example...
Suppose there exists a sleeping devil.
One that's capable of burning
the entire world to the ground.
And what if there was someone with
the ability to wake that devil?
Even if there's someone happened
to be an eight-year-old girl.
Don't you think that for the lives of
every other living being on this planet,
that girl should be put to death?
Stop rambling and get to the point.
What I just told you is the true story of
Nico Robin, her very first transgression.
And now she's accumulated
an entire life of crime.
As far back as she can remember, her very
existence has been nothing but a sin.
The only good she can do this world would
be to forfeit her life
and disappear forever.
That's the misfortune
she carries with her.
She's cursed.
She has no choice but to
accept her fate and die.
Honestly, she should have
died over 20 years ago.
We're merely correcting
a wrong from the past.
It'll be better for everyone else.
when this is over and she's dead. Hey!
That's enough!
Bastard!
I don't want to hear another
word out of you! Pity.
Her death won't come nearly
as quickly as I would like.
Interrogations.
Torture. Slowly.
Repeatedly.
The world government is going
to keep her alive for years,
squeezing out all of her knowledge,
experiences, and intelligence.
Feel no agony before she...
I'm not going to let that happen!
Wait, Robin!
Please don't go in there!
No! Seriously!
That's a really, really,
really bad idea! Stop!
I said wait, not keep going!
Robin!
There you are!
We're in deep trouble.
I'm so happy! Are you okay? Say something!
Why are you doing this?
I went through all that trouble
to sneak in from the outside!
I even took out that
Snoopy government guy!
So that's Nico Robin, huh?
I'd buy that.
Looks like the girl in the
wanted poster, that's for sure.
Let me knock these guys
out, then we'll escape!
We'll run away together and
leave all this behind us, okay?
It's gonna be all right!
It seems that my words
mean nothing to you people
Ha, ha, ha!
Franky, quick!
Detach the third car! Uh-uh! Why?
What are we gonna do? Run!
We're gonna run?
What the heck are you talking about?
You too, Sanji. Get ready.
This will all be over in a flash.
Make sure that Franky doesn't escape.
Right!
Sniper Kong!
Smokestorm!
What kind of a stupid stunt is that?
Come on!
I've got her! Move it!
Put me down! Let go!
All right!
Run!
Whoa!
Turn back!
But we've already come so far!
Venture us!
Yeah, tell us why!
You better give us a reason!
That's not what I meant!
Huh?
I was telling that giant frog that
jumped on the real way to turn back!
He came out a new way!
Get him, get him!
Yokozuna? Go away! Look out!
A giant rock's on the tracks!
Rocky!
Turn back!
Get out of the way! Shut up!
Look out!
Yes!
We did it!
We got Robin back! You know,
I should be happy, but I'm not really
a big fan of this running away stuff.
That smokescreen was such a stupid
idea that it actually surprised them.
Sniper King says,
the plan that involves us not fighting scary
guys like them is the best plan of all.
Doubtful.
Besides, that was too easy.
Yeah, these guys aren't like the others.
We shouldn't let our guard down just yet.
What's that?
Those thorny whips again?!
I've got them.
Now, Line. Right.
Quick, cut those things!
They're pulling us back!
Oh, these guys are powerful.
Did you actually think a
smokescreen would stop us?
Like I said, that was way too easy.
Now remember, don't kill
any of the Straw Hats.
That was our agreement.
Hey, Sniper King. Yeah?
Protect Robin with your life, got it?
What? Right!
I'm going to have to ask
you to let our car go!
What the hell?
His body's like a rock.
I told you, these guys
use some weird moves.
Konkase!
Now that was a pretty powerful kick.
It almost broke through the iron body.
Careful, Bluno.
Don't take him lightly.
He doesn't have a bounty on him,
but he's one of their main fighters.
Robin, hold on a sec.
Wait, what are you doing?
Now, also, with a clutch.
Lobnos, look out!
Hey, Robin, what are you doing?
Didn't you hear me?
Stay out of my business.
Leave me alone.
It can't be.
Hey, buddy, you should
learn to pay attention.
Ah!
Eyebrows!
Your Straw Hats are nuts!
None of you make any damn sense!
All of you are so stubborn, especially when
it has anything to do with your friends!
Well, we've come this far.
So, you want to escape, huh?
Then here's your big chance!
No!
No! No!
That was uncalled for.
Didn't expect that, did you?
I don't understand your intentions.
Why side with them in the first place?
I couldn't take it anymore.
No matter what she said or did.
Those two idiots weren't
gonna leave here without her.
That still doesn't explain
why you're butting in on this.
Wow.
Hey! Listen!
Get out of here!
Don't worry about me!
I got a plan!
When you meet up with Straw Hat,
find some way to get back to Water 7.
Okay!
Franky!
Hold on!
I'm not trying to escape!
I won't run!
Robin!
What's wrong with you?
Cut it out!
There's no point in
trying to pretend anymore.
We know. Okay!
We know what you did!
And we came here to rescue you!
It doesn't matter if they Buster
call us to the ends of the world.
We'll fight them and win.
There's no reason for you to keep
obeying them and throw your life away
You're wrong if there's a Buster Call!
You'll be obliterated.
Tempest!
Sanji!
What just happened?
He came out of nowhere.
How did he do that?
Huh?
Bruno disappeared?
Nothing of the sort.
That's the power of his Dordor fruit.
He can create a door out of thin air,
then use it to travel to another location.
At any rate, don't
bother trying to escape.
It's simply not possible.
Let... Robin... go!
Finger pistol.
Usa!
Iron body.
Your last kick was a lot stronger.
Tired already.
Stubborn one, aren't you? Stop it!
I promise, I have no
intention of running away.
I'll honor the deal, you
don't have to hurt them.
They're the ones who keep attacking me.
What do you expect?
Then let's hurry and leave
before they get up again.
Wait!
It's all right, Robin.
We'll be fine.
I understand what's going on.
You're still hiding something
from us, aren't you?
But there's one less thing.
You can do what you want.
But a pirate isn't allowed
to leave their crew
unless they have their
captain's permission.
So no matter what,
you can always believe in Luffy.
Robin, don't go.
You can say what you like to her!
But she won't break our agreement.
How do you know that?
Long ago.
An island was erased.
That is to say.
The Navy issued a Buster Call.
And burned it to the ground!
without leaving a single trace behind.
The only survivor of that incident was
Nico Robin, still a child at the time.
She never told us.
Five vice-admirals and ten battleships are
a terrifying force for anyone to behold.
But for a child to see
them destroy her home,
well, it's nothing short of a nightmare.
Those thoughts have haunted her for years,
and now that her old nightmare
bears its fangs at her companions,
she no longer has the will
to resist us you bastards!
you knew and you use
that of course we did!
this is sick!
you people are sick you hear me all
of this is for the sake of justice?
i sympathize with her,
but i cannot be swayed.
This isn't over!
Andy's Lobby, Department
of Management here.
Is everything in order
regarding the transfer? Yes.
We will be delivering the
two criminals on schedule.
We can see the island now, so
expect us soon. Understood.
We'll make preparations for your return.
I can't help but feel a bit nostalgic
after five years of absence.
The Nightless Island, Eni's Lobby.